1st: Get hooked
I started pouring a ton of time into research.
Ugh… I still don’t get it!
Oh! That kid with the bell earlier…
Wait—could it be those people, maybe?
Right?
They’re human!
That’s complicated!
So all the skeleton enemies used to be human?
Yeah… that’s complicated.
I ended up taking them out…
And I couldn’t turn them back.
And, uh… I’m kinda curious about what’s going on behind the scenes, too.
So, with that said—
Like, by watching the sto—story again…
You can really—uh—more…
Like, get pulled deeper into the story…
And get even more hooked, you know!
2nd: I’m a sucker for it
Hey—look, look, look, look!
Yeah, yeah, yeah—so like, what Marvel stuff do you recommend?
Like, your top picks.
If you’ve got more, tell me—seriously.
I kinda wanna watch something.
Recommendations, huh…
But at this point, I mean—
Isn’t Doctor Strange the move? (laughs)
True—Doctor Strange is…
It does look fun.
Doctor Strange is, like—
It’s got that whole magic vibe.
Yeah—not just regular action,
It’s got magic stuff too, so…
I think it’ll really click with people who are into that.
Me? I love fantasy and magic—
Like, a LOT.
Seriously?!
Yeah.
Then I think Doctor Strange is totally your thing.
Oh—then maybe I’ll start with that one.
If so.
No way! Watch it, watch it, watch it!
I will, I will!
Yesss! I’m so happy—we’ve got more to talk about now!
I’m so happy!
I’m such a sucker for magic—when someone says “magic,” I’m like, “Ooh, that’s so fantasy!” (laughs)
3rd: Stick your nose in
I’m thinking about buying a gun.
Huh?!
Can just anyone buy one?
Yeah—sit next to him.
And order a whiskey-and-water.
Apparently that’s the signal.
Oh!
Oh, really…
Come to think of it, that guy earlier—
He ordered a whiskey-and-water too.
I wasn’t totally convinced, but—
What I saw just now sealed it.
I’ll come back another day and give it a shot.
A straight-laced guy like you sticks his nose into the underworld, you’re gonna get burned.
4th: Read the room
There are still some really worried Yukimin out there, but—
Like, kinda…
Really, like…
How do I put it—no matter what I do,
“Are you okay? Are you okay?”
“You okay?” like that.
That kind of, like—
There used to be a lot of super worrywart Yukimin.
And stuff!
What else was there…
Like, for every little thing Lamy said or did,
They’d be like, “Is that okay? Is that really okay?”
There were a lot of Yukimin with that vibe.
But now it’s like—
Yukimin these days, you know—
They’re pretty good at reading the room!
Final: Get ahead of it
But man, there aren’t many that seem useful.
For now, I’m going with 3!
Oh—ugh, I hate this.
What, what, what?!
I can’t move!
Heeey! (cute)
What am I supposed to do?!
Like this?!
Get ahead of it, get ahead of it!